https://jessstryker.com/p/privacy-policy-and-terms.html

Please Read before Using Photos:
Photo Use License
Photo FAQs
Click or tap on Photos to Enlarge or view as Slide-Show
Privacy Policy and Terms of Use
Privacy Policy:
Effective June 1, 2018. Last updated June 1, 2018.
This website is intended for use by residents of North America only.
To contact us email JessStryker@gmail.com
Email Address Security.  If you send us an email your email address and message contents may be stored on the email server or backup storage, potentially forever.  Please do NOT use a private or sensitive email address when contacting us.  We assume no liability if your email address or message contents are stolen, compromised, or disclosed publicly.
Why we collect information on users. Information we automatically collect is used to improve our website and to customize it to the individual user. Information you voluntarily provide (such as your email address, comments, and questions) is used to improve the website, answer your questions, communicate with you, insure that you are a real person (as opposed to a robot program), and assist you.  As noted below we may also use information collected to target advertising.
Information automatically collected, possibly without your knowledge (non-personal information).
We use cookies to track your use of our website. This provides us with user statistics which we use to improve our website. Cookies may also be used to deliver customized content to you.
Third party vendors, including Google and Amazon, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website or other websites.
Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting https://www.google.com/settings/ads. (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting www.aboutads.info )
We receive and record information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, some of your software and hardware attributes, and the webpage you are requesting. In most cases this information is automatically sent by your Internet browser to every website you visit.
Information we collect, with your knowledge (personal information).
If you send a question or comment to us we receive and record an email address and any information that you may choose to disclose in your message.
Email messages to and from us may or may not be archived, potentially forever.
Users 17 years old and under. The content of this website is not directed at children under the age of 18. Some material on this website may not be suitable for children. Children under the age of 18 should only use this website under the supervision of a parent or guardian.
Who we share your information with. The website managers, the company that owns this website and employees of that company may have access to the information we collect. We will respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process and provide this information when required, we will also use it to defend ourselves against legal claims if needed. We utilize a website hosting company to maintain the Internet servers for this website. We have noticed that the website hosting company sets it's own cookies (using our website name) when you visit our site, and they may have access to some information collected, particularly the information automatically collected.
How to change your personal information records. You can't change your non-personal information, however you can delete the connection between it and your computer. To delete it simply delete the cookies for this website and our advertisers from your computer. You may email us to request a change to any of your personal information. We do not honor requests to delete email messages we receive from you or send to you, we need them to document correspondence we have had with you.  Such messages may or may not be archived.
Changes to our privacy policy. Changes to our privacy policy will be posted at this website. We generally do not send out email notices of changes.
Copyright Restrictions:
Unless otherwise noted, all of the content of this website is copyrighted by Jess Stryker.  All rights reserved.
The Free Stock Photos are licensed separately from other content to allow for your use, see the Creative Commons license link with each photo for details.
DISCLAIMER:
USE OF ALL MATERIALS ON THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING IMAGES AND PHOTOS, AND THE CONTENT OF REPLIES TO YOUR COMMENTS OR QUESTIONS, IS ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK!
THE INFORMATION IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND ARISING FROM THE COURSE OF DEALING BETWEEN THE PARTIES AND USAGE OF TRADE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF THE CONTENT, PHOTOS, IMAGES, INSTRUCTIONS, AND INFORMATION IS ASSUMED BY THE USER. THE AUTHOR AND/OR PHOTOGRAPHER  WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, OR SIMILAR DAMAGES DUE TO LOSS OF INFORMATION OR DATA, LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, INJURY, OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES, EVEN IF THE AUTHOR AND/OR PHOTOGRAPHER HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR
AND/OR PHOTOGRAPHER'S LIABILITY FOR ANY DAMAGES EVER EXCEED THE PRICE PAID TO THE AUTHOR AND/OR PHOTOGRAPHER FOR THE CONTENT OR INFORMATION, REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF THE CLAIM.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW EXCLUDING WARRANTIES OR LIMITING LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. AS A RESULT, THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS AND/OR EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY. SOME JURISDICTIONS HAVE STATUTORY CONSUMER PROVISIONS WHICH MAY SUPERSEDE SECTIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT.
Limitation of Liability Agreement:
To the maximum extent permitted by law, you agree to waive any claims against Jess Stryker and Jess Stryker & Associates (JS/JSA) arising out of the provision of information to you, except for the sole negligence or willful misconduct of Jess Stryker or Jess Stryker & Associates.
In recognition of the relative risks, rewards and benefits of the content to both you and JS/JSA, the risks have been allocated such that you agree to the fullest extent permitted by law, that JS/JSA's total liability to you for any and all injuries, damages, claims, losses, expenses, or claim expenses arising out of this service from any cause or causes, shall not exceed $100.00. Such causes include, but are not limited to, negligence, errors, omissions, strict liability, breach of contract or breach of warranty.
Certifications, Guarantees and Warranties:
You understand and agree that Jess Stryker and Jess Stryker & Associates (JS/JSA) is not certifying, guaranteeing, or warranting anything.
Dispute Resolution:
You and Jess Stryker and Jess Stryker & Associates (JS/JSA) both agree to non-binding mediation as a first step of any dispute between us.
End
Home
Subscribe to:
Posts (Atom)
Search This Website
Translate this Page
Pages of Photos By Topic
Black Hills South Dakota
(1)
Everglades
(2)
Flowers
(21)
Fruits & Vegetables
(1)
Great Smoky Mountains NP
(2)
Mammoth Cave NP
(2)
Mt Rushmore
(1)
Mt St Helens
(11)
National Parks
(18)
Oregon Caves NM
(1)
Petrified Forest
(14)
Rocky Mountain NP
(3)
Santa Monica Mountains NRA
(1)
Theodore Roosevelt NP
(2)
Wildflowers
(4)
Yellowstone NP
(1)
Zion National Park
(1)
Want to say "Thanks"?
Buy me a hot chocolate
Popular Posts
Theodore Roosevelt National Park, South Unit, North Dakota
Everglades National Park 2 - Flora
Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Cades Cove Area, Tennessee
Zion National Park, Utah
Theodore Roosevelt National Park, North Unit, North Dakota
Oregon Caves National Monument, Oregon
Everglades National Park 1 - Fauna
Mammoth Cave National Park 1, Kentucky
Rocky Mountain National Park, page 3
Mammoth Cave National Park 2, Kentucky
More...
Visit my other websites!Historic Hotels & Lodges.
Photo essays on famous, and not so famous, historic hotels and lodges.Irrigation Tutorials. Sprinkler Warehouse provides a huge collection of free online tutorials on landscape irrigation.
Most of the articles were written by Jess Stryker. Landscape & Home Tutorials.
How to articles on home repairs and landscapes.
